Are you saying that Secretary Hegseth and Rubio are going to be running Venezuela?
And will you be sending in U.S. military troops to provide?
That's working with the people of Venezuela to make sure that we have Venezuela right.
Because for us to just leave, who's going to take over?
I mean, there is nobody to take over.
Don't, don't, don't believe the hype.
Check this out.
That's the vice president of Venezuela, who is there and is having to handle things.
But it's also like, OK, but y'all, I'm not no traitor.
That's my dog.
Like Maduro mi perro, respectfully.
So for those of you talking about, we's free, we's free.
I don't know how to say that in Spanish.
Libertamos?
You wouldn't have been free if Maduro was there or not there.
Having Marco Rubio and Pete Hegseth be the replacement, having the United States be the
replacement does not put you in a better situation.
Remember, this is the same man who said, vote for me, I got y'all, and then deported your
people.
This is the same man who said, vote for me, I got y'all, and then actively reversed your
legitimacy as citizens in this nation.
When is the lesson learned?
The United States is not good for anybody.
Unfortunately, having the United States in your country is not going to bring any reprieve.
It would behoove all of the Venezuelans to come together because the people who saved the
people.
And please don't even fix your moat to say it's none of your business, you're not in
Venezuela.
Well, guess what?
They're literally using the profits of my business as a taxpayer to fund this.
So it is my business.
It's also my business because I am Grenadian, which is a stone's throw away from Venezuela,
so much so that flights were grounded today.
I'm unable to leave because of this military nonsense happening.
It's also my business because I'm a global citizen.
I live on the same globe as you.
You realize that your suffering does not isolate you.
Your suffering is your bridge.
That many people have suffered before you.
Many people are suffering around you and always will.
And all you can do is bring, hopefully, a little light into that suffering.
Enough light so the person who is suffering can begin to comprehend his suffering and begin
to live with it and begin to change it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.